

ABDUL HADI MUZAFFAR NARATIUS

TECHNICAL EXECUTIVE (DEVELOPMENT)

Address: Seri Maya Condo, Jalan Jelatek, Kuala Lumpur

Email: hadimuzaffar@yahoo.com

Mobile. No: +6011-28079613

Linked In: https://www.linkedin.com/in/hadimuzaffar/

GitHub: https://github.com/fateh97

A self-motivated and dedicated web developer who specializes in web design and clean code. Throughout my 4 years experience, I design mockup interfaces, optimise performance and implement effective content based on user's needs. I am a concise communicator and critical thinker who collaborates with clients to bring features and improvements to life. I am also a great team player who collaborates well with other team members to achieve professional excellence and dynamic outcomes.

WORK EXPERIENCES

TECHNICAL EXECUTIVE (DEVELOPMENT)

Prisma Khas Sdn Bhd November 2019 - Present

- Create highly responsive and scalable web application for use in different clients' needs using PHP framework (Codelgniter).
- Create accessible web front-end user interface for new or existing database with combination PHP framework (Codelgniter), JavaScript and SQL.
- Design, test, and debug applications from system development to full system production.
- Create and perform database file backups to client's local directory for recovery purposes.
- Conduct an in-person training for end-users.
- Research latest website applications to keep up with trends and latest technology.
- Support scrum team in reviewing change request and helped intern and junior developers with technical tasks.
- Troubleshoot programming issues and provided help desk support to clients experiencing technical problems.
- Complete training programs to learn new coding languages and application developments.
- Conduct training on software forensics (i2 ANB and i2 iBase) for end users.
- Conduct an installation of IIS, Windows SQL Server and SQL Server Management Studio on client's servers.
- Conduct testing session (UAT, PAT and FAT) with end users before releasing a full production of system.
- Participated in Connected i2 User and Training Conference held in London, England.

WEB DEVELOPER (INTERN)

Swisslink Communication Sdn Bhd March 2019 - May 2019

- Created site layout and user interface using HTML, CSS and PHP practices for company's project using PHP framework (Laravel).
- Collaborated with team to implement design changes, new UI components and new functionality.
- Adapted websites to match changing user preferences and client demands with regular updates.

CERTIFICATE & TRAINING

- Microsoft Azure Data Scientist (March 2022 March 2023)
- AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate (August 2023)
- VA Insight Seminar (March 2023)

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITI TEKNOLOGI MARA (UITM)

Master of Computer Science (Web Technology) 2020 - 2022

• Final CGPA: 3.44

UNIVERSITI TENAGA NASIONAL

Bachelor of Computer Science (Software Engineering) Hons. 2016 - 2019

• Final CGPA: 3.13

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

- ✓ Javascript
- PHP CodeIgniter
- ✓ PHP Laravel
- ✓ CSS

- ✓ AJAX
- Microsoft SQL Server
- ✓ MySQL
- Python

REFERENCE

Mohd Faizul bin Daud
Technical Manager (Development)
Prisma Khas Sdn Bhd
+6016-3264237
faizul@prismakhas.com